《绿箭》前情提要
Previously, on "Arrow"...
我要竞选市长
I'm going to run for mayor.
帕尔默先生最后所录的话
Mr. Palmer's last recorded statement
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
可能能解释他的死因
could shed some light on how he died.
我到底怎么了
What's happening to me?
我们要去南达尔巴特
We're going to Nanda Parbat.
翻译   辰星晓喜迎渣康  小暴徒  Liv
你得满足这种欲望
You need to feed this impulse.
一旦你这么做了  欲望会消退一段时间
Once you do, it will subside for a time.
我想要你救活我妹妹
I want you to bring my sister back to life.
翻译    西西  天青月白  SophiaSaaaga
就算莎拉被救活了
Even if Sara went into the Pit,
从泉水中出来的也不再是莎拉
what came out of the Pit would not be Sara.
你女儿活过来了
Your daughter is alive.
校对   Michael  小闪迷路过 精校   陈小圈
最能表现你爱她的事
The most loving act you can commit
就是让莎拉得到安息
is to return Sara to her final rest.
你不能杀你自己的女儿
You are not going to kill your own daughter.
时间轴风吹来的那片云
她不是我女儿
She's not my daughter!
莎拉
Sara?
特效&后期   咖啡Lee  总监   苹果果
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
真倒霉
Ohh, damn it!
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
你就把垃圾放在那吧
Why don't you just leave that right there?
滚开  贱人
Get off, bitch.
太谢谢你了
Oh, my God, thank you!
星城警局  站住别动
SCPD! Stay where you are.
绿 箭
第四季  第五集
你能来帮忙真是太好了  艾利克斯
I cannot thank you enough for coming on board, Alex.
好在我还是有工资的
Well, then it is a good thing you're paying me, also.
-抱歉久等了  -奥利  这是...
- Sorry for the wait. - Ollie, this is Alex Davis,
艾利克斯·戴维斯  沃尔特推荐的战略官
the new political strategist that Walter recommended.
你到合法投票年龄了吗  艾利克斯
Old enough to vote, Alex?
我没到喝酒的年纪  不也还是开了家酒吧
I owned a bar and I wasn't even old enough to drink.
投票跟喝酒我都到合法年龄了
I am old enough to do both.
你能加入我们  我很开心
Well, I'm glad that you're joining the team,
但我不确定我为什么需要一个战略官
but I don't entirely know why I need a political strategist.
那问题就成了
Well... I guess the question then is,
你想以10%还是90%的票数当选市长呢
do you want to take office with ten percent of the vote or 90?
赢了之后  你还要有能力管理这座城市
After you win, you still need to be able to govern.
你在担心什么
Well, what has you concerned?
-担心我经验不足吗  -这个我不关心
- My lack of experience? - No, we can spin that.
我说的是不为人知的黑暗秘密
No, I'm talking about the kind of closet skeletons
一旦被挖出来就能立刻拉你下台
that could cripple you on your first day in office.
这就是你的查帕奎迪克
Your personal Chappaquiddick.
你是说哈利·波特的那个游戏吗
Wait, like that game from Harry Potter?
不  查帕奎迪克指的是一名获胜在即的候选人
Uh, Chappaquiddick was a scandal involving a can't-lose candidate
他的车掉进了水里
whose campaign fell apart when he was caught having an affair
车里跟他有婚外情的女子淹死了
after his vehicle went underwater
之后他就失去了所有的优势
and the girl he was with drowned.
这个丑闻听起来熟悉吗
Does that sound at all familiar?
指的就是"金牌奎恩"号和莎拉·兰斯的事
Ah, referencing the "Queen's Gambit" and Sara Lance.
懂了
Yeah, got it.
你就要参加首次谈话节目了  对吧
You're about to do your first on-air sit down, right?
没错
Yeah.
贝瑟妮·斯诺
Bethany Snow?
我打包票  她会提莎拉和她姐姐的事
Ten'll get you twenty, she brings up Sara and her sister.
艾利克斯  无意冒犯  我觉得人们不会关心
Alex, all due respect, I don't think that people care
我和劳蕾尔·兰斯和八年前的意外
about my friendship with Laurel Lance and an eight-year-old scandal
目前这座城市正在四分五裂
when the city is disintegrating
还有戴面具持有武器的恶人在背后推波助澜
and there are masked armed men helping it.
且不说提佩尼镇
Not to mention, there's a woman in Pennytown
那个到处杀人的女疯子
that's just running around killing people.
你说得对
You're right.
抱歉  有那么一瞬间
I'm sorry. For a moment,
我都忘了人们关心的只有政治
I forgot how the electorate always cares about the issues
而对丑闻毫无兴趣
and has zero appetite for scandal.
你想团结这座城市
You want this city united?
团结星城
以过去那个花花公子的形象可做不到
You can't do it as the rich kid playboy from the tabloids.
可事实是  劳蕾尔·兰斯会让人想起过去的你
And like it or not, Laurel Lance is a constant reminder of that.
所以从今天开始  任何人提到兰斯小姐
So from this day forward, when anyone brings up Miss Lance,
你都要跟她撇清关系
you distance yourself from her.
来得正好
Hey, just in time.
我在找你
I was looking for you.
怎么了
Why?
你忘了东西
I want to talk to you about something you forgot.
那是什么
What's that?
你还跟我装啊
Is that how you want to play this?
装就装吧  进去
It's fine by me, pal. Let's go.
我不喜欢被人打扰  先生们
I don't appreciate the intrusion, gentlemen.
这里面是通讯仪
There's communications gear in here.
我们出了内奸
We got ourselves a mole.
你觉得奎恩先生是内奸
You believe it's Mr. Queen.
我们在这个岛上待了八个月
Look, we've been on this island eight months
没出过一点事  他来了之后  两个手下
without a single problem. He shows up, suddenly two guys
突然就踩到了地雷  我们的货还被偷了
find landmines and a bunch of drugs go missing.
是啊  康克林  你抓到我了
Yeah, Conklin, you got me.
我不是因为船难被水冲上来的
I didn't, uh, wash up on shore here after a boating accident,
我是接到秘密任务  跳伞下来的
I parachuted in on a secret spy mission.
-你就以骗子的身份归西吧  -得了吧
- You want to die a liar, that's fine by me. - Man, that's enough.
够了  现在这个人更重要
Enough! There are more pressing matters at hand.
如果你们更留意外部威胁
Perhaps if you were focused more on external threats
而不是忙着搞迫害
rather than witch hunts,
早就该抓住这个监视我们的人
you would have caught this man spying on us in the fields.
我可不是在监视  伙计
Oh, I wasn't spying, mate.
你们两个在吵架的家伙有烟吗
Any of you squabblers got a cigarette?
她当时嘟哝了什么
She mumbled something.
听起来像是中东那边的语言
It sounded, I don't know, Middle Eastern?
我等会派一位素描师
All right, um, I'm going to have you sit down
听你说说  行吗
with a sketch artist, ok?
安排一下
Take care of that.
爸爸
Dad.
发生了什么
What happened?
你告诉我啊
You tell me.
有个女人杀了这两个人
These two bodies, dropped by a woman.
也许嫌犯就是几天前
Probably the same woman that's been linked
杀了三个人的那个女人
to the murders of three other skels in the past few days.
一名金发女子
A blonde woman.
-爸  -今晚以前  我什么线索都没有
- Dad, I-- - I didn't know what to make of it until tonight,
现在这个女子猜测
and then this woman here, she suspects,
她说着某种中东语
speaks some kind of Middle Eastern language,
就跟莎拉一样  她还在你那里吗
just like Sara. Is she still at your place?
我一直在找她
I've been looking for her.
你为什么没告诉我  你告诉奎恩了吗
Why didn't you tell me, huh?! You tell Queen?
没有
No!
因为他的反应只会跟你一样
Because he would just see this the same way as you.
结果呢  结果呢
Oh, yeah, and how is that, huh? How is that?!
我必须要...
That Sara is just... a thing
阻止莎拉
that needs to be stopped.
这可是我女儿
This is my daughter.
那你为什么
Then why did I find you
要用枪指着她
with a gun pointed at her head?
我不为此自豪  劳蕾尔
I'm not proud of that, Laurel.
可是她还在杀害无辜
But people are dying.
当初要是我扣下了扳机
And if I pulled that trigger,
也许这些人还活着
maybe they wouldn't be.
我最好在你和奥利弗之前找到她
I'm going to go find Sara, and hopefully I do before you or Oliver.
柯蒂斯  我要你帮我个忙
Curtis, I need you to do something for me.
费莉西蒂  看看我
Felicity, look at me.
运动装和运动包  你能看出我要干什么吧
Gym clothes, gym bag, do either of those suggest anything to you?
你要去健身  可你是技术宅啊
Physical fitness, but then I remembered you're a tech guy.
我还是个获得了铜牌的十项运动员
I'm also a bronze metal decathlete.
铜牌啊
Bronze medal, huh?
2008年在北京得的
Beijing, 2008.
北京  你是说奥运会吗
Beijing, as in the Olympics?
帕尔默先生的录音  你听了吗
Mr. Palmer's recording. Did you play it?
听了  但有些地方不对劲
Yes. There's something off about it.
你确定不是因为这是你前男友的临终遗言吗
You sure it's not the fact that it's a dying declaration from your ex?
我是说  那可是真真正正的
I mean, that is some serious
尼古拉斯·斯帕克斯级别的东西啊
Nicholas Sparks-level stuff.
「美国著名纯爱小说作家」
别发表评论  那作家情感把握得太好了
Don't judge. The man can write emotion.
不  不是那样
No, not that.
也算是啦
I mean, yes, there's that,
但里面录了些很奇怪的东西
but there's still some artifacts playing that shouldn't be there.
不去健身了吗
What about your work-out?
20秒前你貌似并不关心这个问题
Didn't seem to concern you 20 seconds ago.
对不起  费利西蒂  这是我的错
I'm sorry, Felicity, this is my fault.
听到了吗
You hear that?
录音里似乎还有其他东西
Like there's more to the recording.
只是被覆盖了
Something overlapping with it.
我本希望你能帮我清理出来
I was hoping you could clean it up for me.
在你健完身之后
I mean, after your workout.
那个不着急  我很高兴你改变主意
It can wait. I'm glad you changed your mind
决定听听帕尔默先生的遗言了
about hearing Mr. Palmer's final words.
谢谢你  柯蒂斯
Thank you, Curtis.
谢谢你过来
Ah, thank you for coming.
你知道我并无选择
I think we both know I didn't have too much choice.
对  特别是你现在有两个女儿能让我威胁
No. Well, certainly not since you literally doubled the number of daughters I have to hold over you.
还是你听从了我的建议
Or did you take my advice
把莎拉送回了坟墓里
and return Sara to the grave?
你没有听我的建议  真可惜
You didn't take my advice. Pity.
你想要什么
What do you want?!
我要一个崭新的世界
Oh, a new beginning for the world,
一杯梅洛红酒
a nice glass of Merlot--
这俩顺序倒过来也可以
not necessarily in that order.
还想要你帮我一个忙
And for you to do me a favor.
城外48公里有个联邦服务器集群
There's a federal server farm 30 miles outside of the city.
我要你设法进去
I want you to gain access
然后把这个小宝贝插在其中一台电脑上
and plug this little baby into one of the computers.
这东西有什么用
And what's this thing going to do?
这不关你的事
Oh, it's of no concern of yours.
但是别担心
But don't worry.
它并不会毁了这座城市之类的
It's not like it's going to destroy the city or anything.
那个温泉周末不仅帮你理清思路
Whatever that SPA weekend did to clear your head,
它还提高了你的技巧
it also improved your technique.
你现在应付自如了
You're effortless.
是啊  你知道我有多爱我的热石按摩
Yeah, well, you know how I love my hot stone massages.
对了  请战略官的主意挺不错
By the way, that political strategist was a good call.
但他的建议有点严苛了
But his advice was a little harsh.
让你跟劳蕾尔撇清关系
I mean, distancing yourself from Laurel?
那个有点意外  但他有几点说得不错
I wasn't expecting that, but he made a few good points.
比如呢  抛弃你的朋友吗
What, like kicking your friends to the curb?
我和劳蕾尔的友谊...很复杂
Well, my friendship with Laurel is... complicated.
我们已经认识这么久了
We have been in each other's lives for like forever.
你之前和劳蕾尔还有莎拉都恋爱过
I mean, you have been in love with Laurel and Sara,
而劳蕾尔  她...
and Laurel, she--
在我完全迷失的时候
she took me in at CNRI
她把我接纳进创新联合会
when I was completely lost.
甚至还有兰斯队长  好吗
Even Captain Lance, ok,
在妈妈去世后他一直在帮助我们
he has been there for us since mom died.
好吧  所以你想说什么
Ok, but your point?
我想说...
My point is that...
假装不认识你的朋友
pretending that you don't know who your friends are,
这...感觉可不怎么团结啊
it... just doesn't feel very united.
这里是你们的皇太后  费利西蒂·斯莫克
This is your Overlord, Felicity Smoak.
我们弄了个公共广播系统
We have a P.A. system?
这是另一个我可能会后悔的决定
Yet another decision I might live to regret.
怎么了
Hi, what's going on?
代号47在第九大街的某间夜店里
Code 47 at a nightclub on Ninth.
「代号47是同名电脑游戏中的杀手」
一名金发女子发了疯
A blonde woman going crazy.
既然我这个金发在此
And since I'm down here,
那个八成就是我们在找的金发妞了
it's probably the blonde woman we've been looking for.
在佩尼镇杀人的那个女人
The woman who's killing people in Pennytown.
着装准备
Suit up.
救命
Help!
快跑
Run!
你必须停下来
You have got to stop this!
莎拉...
Sara...
你妹妹还活着  她就在外面大街上
Your sister's alive, she's out there,
而且她还在伤人
and she's hurting people.
她怎么活过来的
How is she alive?
复活泉水吗
The Lazarus Pit?
你俩是在南达尔巴特度过的温泉周末
You two spent your spa weekend at Nanda Parbat?
只有那里还订得到房
It was the only place we could get a reservation.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
莎拉嗜血的欲望更强  是不是
The blood lust is worse with Sara, isn't it?
因为她是死而复生
Because you brought her back from death.
没错  而且那不是唯一的问题
Yeah, and that's not the only problem.
她已经不是莎拉了
Sara's not herself.
她变了
She's changed.
为什么你没来找我
Why didn't you come to me with this?
找你干什么
Come to you for what?
向你寻求用魔法复生的专业知识吗
Your expertise with magical resurrection?
为了看你脸上评判的表情吗
Or that judgmental look on your face?
找我帮忙找到她  劳蕾尔
For help finding her, Laurel,
趁她还没受伤  或者去伤害别人
before she gets hurt, or she hurts anyone else.
而且假如现在我脸上有评判的表情
And if I have a judgmental look on my face right now,
那也是因为你用了你不了解的力量
it's because you played with forces that you do not understand,
而如今人们正因此而丧命
and now people are dying because of it.
他是谁
Who's he?
约翰·康斯坦丁
John Constantine.
你老大从我这拿走的名片上也是这么写的
Says so right on the business card your boss took from me.
他身上还带了这个
He had this on his person, as well.
你认出这些地标了吗
Do you recognize these landmarks?
认出了
Yeah.
很好
Good.
无论这位康斯坦丁先生在找什么
Whatever it is Mr. Constantine is looking for,
我要你找到它并带来给我
I want you to find it and bring it back to me.
拜托  我告诉你  你不能信任他
Oh, come on, I'm telling you, you can't trust him!
那你就跟着他
Then you can follow him.
你在干嘛  你真是在祈祷吗
What are you doing? Are you actually praying?
不
No.
不  这些不是祷词  老兄
No, these aren't prayers, mate.
除非你想用他的脑浆重新装饰你这可爱的小屋
Unless you want to redecorate your lovely hut with his brains,
我劝你还是放下武器
I suggest you drop your weapon.
跪在地板上
On the floor.
你逃不出这座岛的
You won't escape this island.
我恰好现在还没打算走
Ah, I don't intend on leaving just yet.
过来  你
Come on, you.
你真的知道那张地图上的地点吗
You really know the place on that map?
-没错  -真的吗
- Yes. - You do?
-真的  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
那你得带我去
You're going to show me.
开车吧
Now drive!
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
莎拉的事吗
About Sara?
劳蕾尔告诉你的
Laurel told you?
不算是
Not exactly.
她还真是一直如此
You got to admire her consistency.
不告诉我她的死  又不告诉你她复活了
Keeps her death secret from me, her resurrection secret from you.
-你还好吗  -我还好吗
- Are you ok? - Am I ok?
我觉得人生中有一些情况
I think there are certain situations in life
是不适用"还好"这个词的
where the word "ok" does not apply.
我们正在努力找到莎拉
Well, we're working on finding Sara.
很好  因为我们还有别的麻烦
Good. Because we got other problems.
这是个远访木马
It's a RAT.
远程访问木马程序
A remote access Trojan.
基本上就是个电脑病毒
Basically a computer virus.
一个被设计用来攻击并抹除特定数据的多变代码
A polymorphic code designed to target and erase certain pieces of data.
这上面加了三层密
It's buried under three levels of encryption.
等我破解出来...
By the time I've cracked it--
达克也许会想为何我还没有帮他搞定这事
Darhk could be wondering why I haven't run his errand for him.
我不会让你独身一人闯入一栋联邦机构的
I'm not sending you to break into a federal facility without back-up.
我不想劳蕾尔知道我和达克的事
I don't want Laurel knowing about me and Darhk.
我没准备让劳蕾尔陪你去
I wasn't suggesting Laurel.
奥利弗有告诉你达克在为一个组织卖命吗
Did Oliver tell you that Darhk works for an organization?
蜂巢
HIVE?
对
Yeah.
蜂巢杀了我哥哥
HIVE had my brother killed.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
而现在  警探  你却告诉我
And now, detective, you're telling me
你在和他们合作
that you were working with them?
为他们工作
For them?
-说来话长  -我有的是时间
- It's a long story. - I've got time.
这座城市不断受到伤害
This city's been hurting.
不是什么新鲜事了
This is nothing new.
达克来找我  说他能帮我们
Darhk comes to me, he offers to help fix it.
说他有厉害的朋友  有很多钱...
He's got powerful friends, he's got money--
他是在幽灵出现前几个月找的我  好吗
and this was months before the Ghosts, all right?
我就以为他是个热心市民
I didn't see him as anything other than a concerned citizen.
那然后呢
Ok, and then?
然后他就一直做好事
Well, then he's doing all of his good stuff,
后来他问我消防队长要去哪度假
and then he asks me where the fire chief is going on his vacation.
我就把度假小屋的地址告诉了他
So I give him the address of his summer cabin.
第二天  小屋就被炸了
Next day, the cabin blows up.
你有质问达克吗
You confront Darhk about this?
当然  结果他给我看劳蕾尔的照片
Of course I did. And that's when he shows me pictures of Laurel.
工作照
At work,
在家里  还有参加互助会的
at home, AA meetings.
所以你哥哥那事
So this thing with your brother,
会影响
is it going to be a problem
我们的合作吗
for us working together?
不会  警探
No, detective.
因为你在达克身边会帮我们除掉蜂巢
Because you being next to Darhk is going to help us take down HIVE.
找到被莎拉杀害的人的共同点了吗
Any luck connecting Sara's victims?
她杀的都是抢劫犯和街头混混
Just that she's only killed muggers and street thugs.
我还以难以相信  我们在谈论的人
I still can't believe that it's Sara
是莎拉
we're talking about.
难以相信她还活着  我知道是有可能的
That she's alive. I mean, I know how it's possible,
但是  怎么可能呢
but how is it possible?
这个世界的...
The world is a much more...
复杂程度是大多数人都难以置信的
complicated place than most people are comfortable believing.
我收到了雷之前的一条消息
I received an old message from Ray,
就在他死前留下的
in the moment right before he died.
我差点没听
I almost didn't listen to it,
因为...
because...
我不想...再次陷入悲痛
I didn't--I didn't want to feel that grief again.
先不说僵尸末日的威胁
The threat of zombie apocalypse aside,
如果能不用面对离别之痛
isn't it kind of nice not having to deal
不是挺好的吗
with the pain of saying good-bye?
真这么简单就好了
Well, if it were that simple.
我没有一天
Not a day goes by that I don't
不想念我爸妈
miss my parents,
还有汤米
or Tommy.
我一直在想  如果可以再与他们
And I think about what I would...
共度一分钟  我愿意付出什么代价
give just to spend another minute with them,
但是莎拉的复活
but what's happening with Sara isn't
没有抚慰任何人的伤痛  而是加深了痛苦
healing anyone's pain. It's just--it's making it worse.
她差点杀了那两个女孩
She almost killed those two girls.
她为什么要对付她们呢
I mean, why would she even go after them?
她的心智有点残缺不全
Her marble collection's a little incomplete.
我乱猜的
Just guessing.
她们有什么共同点吗
Well, they have something in common?
女服务员叫斯蒂芬妮·丹格斯
The waitress was Stephanie Dangess,
斯蒂芬妮·丹格斯
俱乐部里的姑娘叫琳迪赛·鲍逊
and the girl at the club was Lindsay Paulson.
琳迪赛·鲍逊
天呐  这两个姑娘...
Oh, my God, both these girls--
长得都像西娅
they look like Thea.
最不想要的就是听人说教了
Last thing I want, judgment for tonight.
奥利  来电
我不信莎拉会做这种事
I just can't believe that Sara would do something like this.
她不是莎拉
She's not Sara.
不  不是的
No, that's not it.
你觉得怎么样
How you feeling?
莎拉  她...
Ah, Sara, she--
我知道  你安全了
Ah, I know, it's ok. You're safe.
她想杀我
She tried to kill me.
她神志不清
She's not in her right mind.
你根本不明白
You have no idea.
是复活泉水
This is the Pit.
她跟我当时的情况一样
She's going through the same thing I am.
西娅  我以为你已经好多了
Thea, I thought that you were better.
我去南达尔巴特的时候  我...
When I went to Nanda Parbat, I...
杀了两个人
killed two guys.
马尔科姆...
Malcolm--
马尔科姆就把他们拱手相送
Malcolm served them up on a platter for me,
帮我抑制嗜血的心性
and... helped keep my blood lust at bay.
我的天
Oh, my God.
还好你没事  谢天谢地
Thank God you're all right.
劳蕾尔  跟我来
Laurel, come with me.
西娅还好吗
Is Thea ok?
不好
No.
不止是西娅住院的事
Not only is Thea hospitalized,
我要说梅林放任她杀人
but she has Merlyn influencing her to kill people.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
就是你去南达尔巴特的秘密之行里
Oh, just another thing that happened
发生的另一件事
on your secret trip to Nanda Parbat.
我没告诉你我带你妹妹
Hey! I didn't tell you that I took my sister
去南达尔巴特  就是因为我知道你不会同意
to Nanda Parbat because I knew that you wouldn't approve.
你为什么不告诉你之前带西娅去过
Why didn't you tell me you took Thea?
跟这事有什么关系
What does that have to do with anything?!
你的虚伪让我难以忍受
It's the hypocrisy that I can't stand!
怎么
What?
你为你妹妹做什么都行
It's ok for you to do whatever you have to for your sister,
我为我妹妹做同样的事就不行吗
but it's not ok for me to do the same to mine?
莎拉死了
Sara was dead.
西娅没有
Thea wasn't.
那你七个月前为什么不告诉我西娅的事
Then why didn't you tell me about Thea seven months ago?
因为你高高在上  不愿平等相待
Because you don't see me as an equal.
什么  别这样
What? Oh, come on.
劳蕾尔  我当然有平等相待
Laurel, of course I see you as an equal.
不  你没有  你从来就没有过
No, you don't! You never have.
你从没告诉我你就是绿箭...
You never told me that you were the Arrow--
你小声点
Keep your voice down!
成了黑金丝雀
Becoming the Black Canary,
你也从没打算告诉我
and you never would have told me
有办法可以救我妹妹
that there's a way to save my sister.
我妹妹现在神志不清
My sister, she's out of her mind right now.
是因为我所做的事
Because of something that I did.
是因为我所做的决定
A decision that I made.
你有没有停下来想过  哪怕一秒钟
Did you ever just stop and think for one second
想一想我的处境
about what I might be going through?
西娅的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about what happened to Thea.
真的很抱歉  我爱你的家人...
I really am. I love your family--
我一直都爱你们
I always have.
我就希望你偶尔也能为我的家人着想
I just wish that sometimes you would give a damn about mine.
下车
Get out.
确定就是这里吗
You're sure this is the place?
就是这里
It's the place.
到底怎么回事  你是谁
What's going on, who are you?
你知道你的老大在这座岛上
How much do you know about what your boss
究竟在干什么吗  伙计
is really doing on this island, mate?
他制毒
He's making drugs.
这样倒好了
If only.
你朋友瑞特是个危险分子
Your friend Reiter, he's the dangerous sort.
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
意思就是这座岛上有些东西
It means there are things on this island
是坏人绝不能染指的
that bad people shouldn't have access to.
这话居然出自一个拿枪对着我脑袋的人之口
Says the guy with a gun pointed at my head.
我不是坏人
I'm not a bad guy.
确实有点难以捉摸
A little hard scrabble, sure,
但我是站在正义这边的  哥们
but, uh, I'm on the side of the angels, mate.
至少在他们想尽办法折磨我的时候是的
At least when they're busy trying to screw me over.
你没的说错  就是这里
You're right. This is the spot.
[咒语]
怎么  你以前没见过魔法吗
What? You've never seen magic before?
来吧  爱丽丝
Well, go on then, Alice.
钻进兔子洞吧
Down the rabbit hole you go.
干得不错  我们进来了
Nice job getting us in.
你这技能是给奎恩工作之前还是之后学会的
You learn how to do that before or after working for Queen?
改天再告诉你
Save that for another story.
好吧
Yeah, I bet.
这是接入点吗
Is this the access point?
是的  看起来像是
Yeah, yeah, looks like it.
盯着点那些私人保安
All right, keep an eye out for rent-a-cops,
这种事对我的职业前景没什么好处
'cause it wouldn't do my career prospects too much good.
五十二号联邦网络设施
成功了吗
It working?
我想是的  看起来病毒正在清除人们的文件
Yeah, I think so. Looks like the virus is erasing files on people.
程序状态:运行中
什么样的人  为什么
Which people, and why?
问得好
Both really good questions.
你怎么  在这里
What are you... doing here?
等你醒来
Waiting for you to wake up.
西娅  我该向你道歉
Thea, I owe you an apology.
不  你没必要
No, no, there's no need
为任何事道歉
for you to apologize for anything.
不  有必要
Yes, I do.
我在不知道如何控制莎拉的情况下把她复活了
I brought Sara back without any idea of how to control her.
可是我是之前杀她的那个人
I'm the one who killed her in the first place.
这也是她追杀我的原因
That-- that's why she's after me, you know.
驱使着她的这种杀戮的欲望
This blood lust she's consumed by...
跟我想到拉斯时候的感觉一样
it's the same pain I feel when I think about Ra's.
我不明白
I don't understand.
因为我被驱使着去杀的人
Because the person that I'm driven to kill,
也就是那个杀了我的人  已经死了
the one who killed me is already dead.
西娅  你在说些什么
Thea, what are you talking about?
她杀掉我后就会没事了
As soon as she kills me, she'll be OK.
如果拯救莎拉的唯一办法是杀死你
If the only way to save Sara is to kill you,
那这根本就不是解决办法
then that's no cure at all.
还要多久
How much longer?
两分钟
Two minutes.
安德鲁·狄格尔
等等  刚才那是什么
Wait, wait, what was that?
-怎么了  -我刚才看到我哥哥的名字了
- What is it?  - I just saw my brother's name.
怎么回事
What is that all about?
你做了什么
What'd you do?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything!
不管被删掉的是什么  我得找回来
I just have to get back to whatever it is that's been erased.
不不不  我们没时间了
No, no, no, we don't have time.
保安随时都会来
Security's going to be on their way now.
我不会走的
I'm not leaving.
把枪放下  快点
Drop it! Drop it now!
嘿  没事了  没事了
Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's all right, it's all right!
我是星城警察局的兰斯警官
Captain Lance, Star City police department.
我跟踪这个黑客到这里
I just tracked this hacker here.
好了  听我说
All right. Now, look,
去叫人来增援
go get some back-up, all right?
叫人来  快点
Call this in, come on, go, go!
故事编得不错  把我敲晕之前
It's a good story. I just wish you would have told me
跟我说一声就更好了
before you gave me a concussion.
走吧  那样的话看起来就太假了
Come on. Then it wouldn't have looked real.
我没想到你还在这
I didn't know you were still here.
我来只是确认西娅没事
Yeah, I just came to make sure Thea was ok.
之前没机会这么做
I didn't have a chance to before, so.
她在睡觉
She's sleeping.
马上就睡着了
Trying to.
我
Look, I--
我知道你为什么来这
I know why you're here.
好吧  我懂了
OK, I get it.
我想让你明白
I want you to know that it's--
这没什么
It's OK.
下手吧
I want you to do it.
[咒语]
关于我之前说的
About what I said before--
你说过你的打算
You said some things that you meant.
西娅
Thea!
你确定要待在这吗
You sure you want to be here?
我一直都很讨厌医院
I hated hospitals before tonight.
今天这情况我就更不用住院了
It's just another excuse to stay away.
在医院的时候  我看着莎拉的眼睛
At the hospital, I looked Sara in the eyes.
那不是她
She wasn't there.
什么意思
What does that mean?
泉水不应该用在死人身上
The pit is not supposed to be used on the dead.
它只是把莎拉的肉体唤醒了
It brought Sara's body back,
但现在发生的一切
but all of this is happening...
都是因为她的灵魂不在里面
Because it didn't restore her soul.
我们还是要找到她
We still need to find her, OK?
你搬来和劳蕾尔一起住以前莎拉就死了
Sara died long before you moved in with Laurel,
并且她很清楚你在医院的哪间病房
and she knew exactly which hospital room to look for you in.
难道你认为某种程度上莎拉可以感知到西娅吗
What, you think Sara can sense Thea somehow?
说到这让我想起了超能力者
And here I was just wrapping my mind around meta humans.
等等  我们俩都在复活泉水里浸泡过
Wait, we've both been in the Pit.
也许  这赋予了我们某种关联
Maybe-- maybe that gives us some type of connection.
我们可以利用的关联
A connection we can use.
西娅  你刚出院
Thea, you just got out of the hospital.
我不想拿你当诱饵
I don't want to use you as bait.
我觉得你不再管事
Well, I guess it's a good thing
是件好事
you're not in charge anymore.
我们会帮她的  奥利弗  所有人
We'll have her back, Oliver. All of us.
我不明白  你是怎么...
I don't understand. How did you...
这就是魔法的神奇之处
Well, that's the great thing about magic.
无法解释
Can't be explained.
这世界上有些地方跟这个世界一样古老
There are places in this world as old as the world.
有关联的地方
Places of nexus,
会把坏人吸引过去
draw bad people to them.
这座岛就是这种地方
This island is such place.
你在这里不是偶然
It's no accident that you're here.
我来猜猜
Let me guess--
禁止入内
"Do not enter."
应该是  心灵纯净的人才能进
More like, only for the pure of heart.
你不符合条件  哥们
That's not you, mate.
你在这啊  美丽的姑娘
There you are, my pretty girl.
你怎么知道是个姑娘
How do you know it's a girl?
我也会点小把戏
I can do that trick, too.
聪明的小伙子
Clever boy.
我通常都会更巧妙些
I'd usually be more artful,
但我这会有点赶时间
But I'm on something of a clock.
过来
Get back!
我也不是坏人
I'm not a bad guy, either.
任务完成了
Mission accomplished.
很好
Well done.
你是想吃个纸杯蛋糕再走吗
Are you sticking around for a cupcake or something?
你让我干的这件事
This thing you had me do,
我看到了一些你删除掉的名字
I saw some of the names you had erased.
全都是军人
All military.
看来你是个勒德分子
And here I had you pegged for a Luddite.
「强烈反对机械化或自动化的人」
学得倒挺快
Fast learner.
里面有个名字  安德鲁·狄格尔警官
One of those names-- Sergeant Andrew Diggle.
这人怎么了
What is to you?
他六年前就死了
He died six years ago.
为什么要抹去一个死人的档案
Why are you erasing the record of a dead man?
这样吧  我告诉你
You know what, I'm going to tell you.
全是看在你如此高效地完成了任务的份上
And only because you completed your task with such efficiency.
我们雇了杀手
We hired an assassin
除掉了狄格尔警官
to murder Sergeant Diggle.
为什么
Why?
阿富汗是个很有趣的地方
Afghanistan's an interesting place,
那里有很多
replete with opportunities
让有魄力的军人参与的机会
for an enterprising enlisted man to engage in.
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
毒品  武器  谋杀
Drugs, weapons, murder.
这位狄格尔警官是个勤奋努力的人
Your Sergeant Diggle was an eager beaver.
不幸的是  我们的组织
Unfortunately for him, our organization
也参与了那些交易
weaved itself into that part of the world,
你也知道  我们不喜欢有同行
and as you know, we don't play well with others.
所以就要杀了他吗
So you had him killed?
怎么  这个人是你的好朋友吗
What is this guy, your best buddy?
我没看见你与犯罪头目有什么来往
I don't see you associating yourself with crime lords.
当然我除外
Present company excepted.
说完了吗
Now, are we done?
就位
Set.
不得不说  现在回到这里让我感觉很奇怪
I have to say, it feels really weird being back here right now.
别担心  大家都就位了
Don't worry. Everyone's in position.
没什么  好吧
It's nothing, OK?
我真不觉得这能有用
I-- I don't think this is going to actually work.
天呐  刚才的话我收回
Oh, God, I take that back.
带她离开
Get her out of here!
爸爸是对的
Dad was right.
你的体内已经没有灵魂了  莎拉
There's nothing left inside of you, Sara!
-麻醉箭  -不
- Tranq arrow. - ?No.
不  你自己说的  她已经没有灵魂了
No, you said it yourself, she has no soul.
劳蕾尔
Laurel...
我们把她的灵魂找回来
let's get it back.
好
Right.
奥利弗
Oliver. ?
约翰
John.
十几年没见了  伙计
It's been a dog's age, mate.
不止  还记得你欠我个人情吗
More than. Do you remember that favor you owe me?
我没指望你会让我忘记
I hardly expect you to let me forget about that.
你最快多久可以到星城
How quickly can you get to Star City?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
约翰·康斯坦丁
怎么  你要给我妹妹驱魔吗
So what, you're going to perform some kind of exorcism on my sister?
不  驱魔是驱赶恶魔的躯体
No, an exorcism is a removal of demonic possession.
你妹妹需要的是招魂
What your sister needs is a restitutionem,
把她的灵魂复位
the restoration of her soul to her body.
以前做过这种仪式吗
And you've done this before?
做过一次  一年前吧
Once. Maybe a year ago.
不过别担心  这就跟骑自行车一样简单
But don't worry, it's just like riding a bike.
我想一定有很多准备工作要做
I'm sure we have a lot of work to do to prepare.
你有列出清单来吧
I assume you brought a list?
抱歉  我没那么多时间
Apologies. I didn't have time to translate that
把那些阿拉姆语都翻译出来
from its original Aramaic.
早知道你身边这么多美女  奥利弗
You know, if I knew you were surrounded by so many pretty girls, Oliver,
我早就过来看你了
I would have stopped by sooner.
奥利弗从哪找来这么个人  卢克索吗
Where did Oliver find this guy, the Luxor?
很高兴奥利弗这个以前的朋友
Oh, I'm just glad that the latest person from Oliver's past
不是另一个美女
is not another gorgeous woman.
我连问都不想问
I'm not even going to ask.
你收到我的信息了
You got my message.
很高兴你能来
I'm so happy you came.
我也是她的父亲
I'm her father, too.
实在不想说这话
I hate to be the one to say this,
但万一出什么意外呢
but what if something goes wrong?
别担心  如果出意外
Oh, don't worry. If things go wrong,
那我们都会死  根本不用担心了
then we'll all be too dead to care.
那好  现在我们只需要...
Well, then. Now we just need a--
我想你需要的一切都在这里了
I think I got everything in here that you wanted,
虽然我并不确定
although I am not entirely sure
你要一根死孔雀的毛干什么
what you need a dead peacock feather for.
真不错
Oh, nice one.
我都痒了好几个小时了
That's been bugging me for hours.
现在
Now,
我这里的液体只够我和你们中的两个人
I've only got enough juice to send myself and two of you
到另一个领域再回来的
to the other realm and back, so.
我觉得我应该去
Oh, I think it should be me.
她变成现在这样都是因为我
I'm the reason why she's like this right now.
无意冒犯  亲爱的  不过据我所知
No offense, love, but from what I hear,
你并不是那个能把莎拉最好的一面
you're not exactly bringing out the best
引出来的人  是不是
in Sara right now, are you?
劳蕾尔
Laurel.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
相信我  这会奏效的
Trust me when I tell you this will work.
对了  还有一件事
Oh, there's one more thing.
把她灵魂锁起来的那个东西
Whatever's locked her soul away,
是不会轻易就交出来的
it's not going to give it over without a fight.
做好准备
So be ready.
好了
All right, then.
表演开始
On with the show.
[咒语]
Pelako ameso yobe eleggua
imbone ukuchila panshita.
[咒语]
De domino vestro, aliquis.
Et stabit de domino vestro. Audite vocem meam.
[咒语]
Ancor, anchor, candones helosi
et vos eleutis phugori...
[咒语]
De cruinne-ce agus akasha
seall me do solas!
奥利弗
Oliver!
我有过比这更醉的感觉
Well, I've had worse hangovers.
现在我们应该做什么
So what are we supposed to do now?
劳蕾尔  别去
Laurel, no!
这还是头一遭
This is new.
所以你才需要我
Well, new is why you brought me along.
救命
Help.
别去  别去  别去
No, no, no, no.
我不能就这么站在这
Well, I'm not going to just stand here!
我们需要一个向导
We need a tour guide.
这边
This way.
除非你们想永远被困在这里
Unless you want to be trapped here for all eternity.
这就是锁住了莎拉灵魂的东西吗
This is what locked away Sara's soul?
人类的大脑是这么感知的
How the human mind perceives it, anyway.
救命
Help!
过去帮忙  你们必须一起把她救出来
Get to the Pit. You need to work together to get her out.
我来对付这位新朋友
I'll take care of our new friend.
你对我有所求是吗
You want some of me?
你们俩抓紧时间
You know, any time today would be good.
出来吧  莎拉
Come on, Sara.
劳蕾尔
Laurel.
你没事
You're all right.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's going to be all right.
发生什么事了
What happened?
她怎么样
What is she?
我们...
Did we...
莎拉
Sara!
谢谢你  约翰  我欠你个人情
Thank you, John. I owe you one.
是我之前欠你的  伙计
I believe I owed you one, mate.
就算我们扯平了吧
Hows about we just call it even?
无论何时何地  只要需要我
How about any time, anywhere you need me,
我就会来
I'll be there.
我接受
I'll take that.
我脖子后面的头发
You know, the hair on the back of my neck
自从一来到这里就一直竖着呢
has been standing up since the moment I got into town.
可能是因为我们现在的问题
That is probably our current problem--
达米恩·达克
Damian Darhk.
你听说过他
Ohh, you've heard of him.
你要小心他  老兄
You watch yourself on that one, mate.
你之前所见的那些
He'll make what you saw
跟他比起来都不算什么了
in the other realm look like a bloody gnat.
有什么有用的建议吗
Any helpful advice?
有  趁你现在还可以  赶紧离开
Yeah. Leave town. While you still can.
他还挺有特殊魅力的
Well, he's a very specific kind of yummy.
好吧  我要假装没有听见你刚才说了什么
Oh! I'm going to pretend I didn't hear you just say that.
我们没事了吗
Are-- are we OK?
我一直在等着你对我大发脾气
I mean, I just keep waiting for you to blow up at me.
因为你骗我去南达尔巴特的事吗
Because you lied to me about Nanda Parbat?
是的
Yeah.
西娅  我没有权利对任何人生气
Thea, I don't have the right to be mad
就因为他们有秘密
at anyone for keeping secrets.
但我很抱歉让你觉得你需要瞒着我
But I'm sorry that I made you feel as though you had to.
过来
Come here.
谢了  老兄  欠你一次
Thanks, mate. I owe you one.
这些都是些什么
What the hell is all this?
这个是荷鲁斯之眼
Oh, this is the Orb of Horus.
实际上是本魔法书
It's actually a grimoire.
一本古老的咒语书
An ancient spell book.
是你问的
You asked.
那你要怎么处理它
And what are you going to do with it?
和我之前找到的那些魔法物品一样
Same as I do with all the other mystical objects I find--
把它保存在一个安全的地方
I keep them in a safe place,
远离巴伦·瑞特这样的人
away from the Baron Reiters of this world.
记住我告诉你关于这座岛的事情  老兄
Remember what I told you about this island, mate.
这个瑞特到这里来可不只是为了毒品
This Reiter bloke is not only here for the narcotics.
但是话说回来  这和你没有关系  对吧
But then again, it's not your problem, is it?
和我一起回去吧
Come back with me.
我在南海岸有艘船
I've got a boat on the southern shore.
你看到营地的那些人了
You saw those people at camp.
我不能把他们留下
I can't leave them behind.
你可真是个大英雄
Well, aren't you the hero?
我也不能这样空手回去
I also can't come back empty-handed.
康克林已经很怀疑我了
Conklin suspects me enough as it is.
有道理
Fair enough.
给
Here.
像瑞特那样的傻瓜
Goons like Reiter,
他们只对这样的东西感兴趣
they're only interested in the sparkly bits, anyway.
真正的力量在咒语中
The real power is in the spell.
来  我给你展示下
Here. Here, I'll show you.
[咒语]
Yateeka masaha la hasra laha
watahseen hayda albaled almodeef
那你的衣服撩起来
Lift up your shirt, mate?
什么
What?
你刚刚做了什么
What the hell did you just do?
我给了你一个对抗瑞特的保障
I gave you some insurance against Reiter.
等时机成熟
And when the time comes,
你会知道怎么用的
you'll know how to use it.
好吧  我想我们该做的已经做完了
Now, I believe, that concludes our business.
你得朝我脸上打一拳
I-- I need you to punch me in the face.
没错  我试图逃跑时把你打伤了  对吧
Right. My escape attempt left a bruise, right?
好吧  我必须要警告你
All right. I must warn you,
我的右勾拳很重的
I've got a hell of a right hook.
我没事了
I'm-- I'm fine.
谢谢你
Thanks very much.
记住你的核心理念
All right, so just stay on message.
团结  社区团结
Unity, united community.
团结  记住了
United. Got it.
好的
All right.
劳蕾尔
Hey, Laurel.
也许我应该教教你
Ok, maybe we need to work on your understanding
"撇清关系"的含义
of the phrase "distance yourself."
除非你坚持
Only if you insist on
要对我的朋友们使用这一策略
continuing to use it when it relates to my friends.
好吧
OK.
这是你的竞选
It's your campaign.
不论你是否当选  你都要付我钱
You pay me whether you win or lose.
我去保证他不会辞职
I am going to go keep him from quitting.
但是我现在非常为你骄傲
But I'm very proud of you right now.
莎拉怎么样了
How's Sara?
在休息
Resting.
看来找回自己的灵魂是很累人的
It turns out that getting your soul back is exhausting.
是的
Yeah.
奥利
Ollie...
我不知道我应该怎么才能表示我的感谢
I don't know how I'm ever going to be able to thank you.
就是这样
Just like that.
好吧  谢谢你
Well, thank you.
谢谢你今晚邀请我
And thank you for inviting me here tonight.
尤其我对你在医院里说了那些话之后
After what I said to you in the hospital,
我以为我是你最不想见的人
I thought that I'd be the last person you'd want to see.
你没说错  我
Well, you were right. I--
我并没有做到一个好朋友该做的
I haven't always been the best friend for you,
但是我很感激有这个机会
but I--I'd be grateful for the opportunity
能够重新开始
to try and start to be.
我怎么能拒绝一个
How can I say no to the man
拯救了我妹妹灵魂的人呢
that helped me save my sister's soul?
错误伤害了一些我最亲近的人
Mistakes that have hurt people close to me.
但是我不会躲避过去
But I'm not here to run from the past.
因为过去是为了
Because the past has contributed to making--
我还以为你会和莎拉一起庆祝
I thought you'd be out celebrating with Sara.
以后有的是机会
Yeah, there's enough time for that.
请进
Please.
我想我欠你一样东西
I figured I owed you something.
我问过达克关于你哥哥的事情
I asked Darhk about your brother.
他给了我一些东西
He gave me something.
你不一定要看
You don't have to read this.
你可以保持你记忆中他的样子
You can remember your brother how you knew him.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
是的  这是真的
Yeah, it's legit.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
机密文件
谢谢你  警探
Thank you, Detective.
给你一个打击并不值得你的感谢
Gut punch doesn't deserve a thank you.
是我想知道为什么
I wanted to know why...
蜂巢要杀死我哥哥
H.I.V.E. had my brother killed,
现在我知道了  所以
and now I do, so...
费利西蒂  欢迎回来  欢迎  欢迎
Felicity! Welcome back! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
你干了多少这些饮料
How many of these have you drank?
应该是"喝了"  喝了很多  但是值得
It's "drunk," actually, and many. But worth it.
你清理出雷留言里的内容了吗
You cleared up the rest of Ray's message?
我想是的  录音回放正好
I think so. The playback was rendering
在你进来时准备好  时机刚刚好
when you came in. So, propitious timing.
你以后在工作时间里
Ok, you're not even allowed to say "energy drink"
连"能量饮料"这个词都不准提了
while on company time ever again.
没事  我想反正我也
That's ok. I think I might be having
会得心脏病的
a cardiac incident, anyway.
留言  来看看  我正要给你打电话呢
So, the message, check it out. I was just about to call you.
等等  我手机在哪
Wait, where's my phone.
等等  我已经给你打电话了吗
Wait, did I call you already?
柯蒂斯
Curtis!
我很抱歉  费利西蒂  这是我的错
I'm sorry, Felicity, this is my fault.
都是因为我瞎搞机械护甲和
I--I got myself into this mess screwing around
纳米技术才惹来这个祸事
with my exosuit and nanotechnology.
但是现在自我检讨
But recriminations probably aren't
并非最紧要的
the best use of this limited bandwidth.
我想告诉你的是
What I need you to know is,
我还活着  但我深陷困境
I'm alive, and I'm in trouble.